

Yuri Gorelik

QA Engineer



+375-29-2547147



https://www.linkedin.com/in/yuri-gorelik/



yura114345@tut.by



https://yura114345.github.io/yuri_gorelik.github.io/

Software testing specialist with a focus on functional testing of mobile and Web-based applications with 1+ year experience. I'm hardworking and initiative person and passionate about quality control, like to learn new technologies and always looking for ways to improve my work, currently I'm developing in the direction of automation.



Work History

2021/01 - Current

QA Engineer

Remedy Product Studio - Minsk, Belarus

- Web testing
- Mobile applications testing (for Android and iOS)
- Test documentation creation: test cases, bug reports (Instabug)
- Requirements analysis
- Functional testing and regression testing
- REST API testing (GraphQL)

2010/07 - 2020/12

Senior Engineer

Belgiprodor - Minsk, Belarus

- Data processing with software systems AutoCAD and CREDO
- Preparing reports and supporting technical and test documentation
- Executive shooting and field supervision of projects
- Working with high-precision equipment (GPS Topcon; Sokkia, Leica; digital level Trimble)



Education

2021/07 - 2021/11

Automation QA Engineer (Python)

Teach Me Skills – Minsk, Belarus

- Basic knowledge of Python language
- Knowledge of OOP in Python
- Pytest, Unittest
- Working with Git (Bitbucket), Linux (Bash)
- Selenium WebDriver (CSS-locators, xPAth, PageObject)
- Working with REST API (JSON, XML, YAML)
- Basic knowledge of SQL (MySQL), CI/CD (Docker, Jenkins, Allure)

2020/08 - 2020/10

Software Testing Engineer. Professional Level

IT Academy BELHARD - Minsk, Belarus

- Web applications testing (DevTools)
- REST API testing (HTTP Headers, HTTP Body, Postman)
- Performance testing (JMeter)
- Mobile app testing basics (Android Studio, Xcode, Charles Proxy)
- Functional test automation (IntelliJ IDEA, Selenium IDE)
- SQL basics for testing (MySQL)
- Version control systems (Git, GitHub, SourceTree)

2020/02 - 2020/03

Software Testing Engineer

IT Academy BELHARD - Minsk, Belarus

- · Software development models and methodologies
- Types and levels in software testing
- Test design techniques
- Test documentation development (bug report, checklist, test case, test plan)
- Bug tracking systems (Jira, Trello)

2017/09 - 2017/10

Java Programming Language

IBA Institute of IT&Business Administration – Minsk, Belarus

- Basic knowledge of Java language
- Identifiers, keywords, Java data types
- Knowledge of OOP in Java

2005/09 - 2010/05

Bachelor's Degree in Engineering

Belarusian National Technical University - Minsk, Belarus

Transport Communications: Road Design



Key Skills

- Mobile applications testing
- Web testing
- API testing
- Test documentation creation (checklist, test case, bug report)
- Testing automation
- Performance, usability, and compatibility testing
- Functional and regression testing



Tools

- MySQL PyCharm • Git
- GitHub DevTools
- Selenium WebDriver
- Figma
- CSS
- HTML

- Jira
- Confluence
- Jenkins Docker
- Postman
- JMeter
- Charles
- Android Studio

Xcode



Languages

English





- Running, OCR (Obstacle Course Racing)
- Football
- Cooking